<resources>
    <string name="app_name">DungeonAndDragonHelper</string>
    <string name="welcome"><![CDATA[Welcome to the D&D world]]></string>
    <string name="Home"><![CDATA[D&D Helper Home]]></string>
    <string name="Map_button">Click to go to map generation</string>
    <string name="start_button">Start your Adventure!</string>
    <string name="generate_map">Generate Map</string>
    <string name="get">Get map</string>
    <string name="go_home">Home</string>
    <string name="save_map">Save</string>
    <string name="welcome_adventure">Welcome to chapter one.</string>
    <string name="begin">Your adventure begins with _________ (Tap to select options in blank spaces)</string>
    <string name="heroes_in_party">heroes in your party</string>
    <string name="partyMembers">Your adventure begins, the adventurers in your party are \u0020</string>
    <string name="ch2SelectedTown">The adventuring party makes their way to the town of \u0020</string>
    <string name="ch2SelectedSideQuest">Your party learns of a quest from the town to \u0020</string>
    <string name="nextChapter">Next Chapter</string>
    <string name="ch2">Chapter Two</string>
    <string name="ch2Start">Your adventure takes its next step, your party arrives in the town of ____ (Tap to select town)</string>
    <string name="ch2town2">Valisten</string>
    <string name="ch2town1">Listalum</string>
    <string name="ch2town3">Draker</string>
    <string name="questObjective">Your adventuring parties main quest objective is _____</string>
    <string name="selectedQuest">Your parties main objective in this campaign is to \u0020</string>
    <string name="quest3">Find and explore the mythical labyrinth unknown to all and guarded by a great warlock, no-one has returned alive.</string>
    <string name="quest2">Retrieve the artifact of power from an evil wizard who stole it.</string>
    <string name="quest1">Defeat the Dark Lord terrorising the land and bring back the light.</string>
    <string name="party1">One</string>
    <string name="party2">Two</string>
    <string name="party3">Three</string>
    <string name="party4">Four</string>
    <string name="chapterOneTown">Your adventuring party begins in the town of _____</string>
    <string name="ch1town1">Rivera</string>
    <string name="ch1town2">Valstak</string>
    <string name="ch1town3">Leyvin</string>
    <string name="ch1SelectedTown">Your adventuring party begins their journey in the town of \u0020</string>
    <string name="genTownButton">Generate town</string>
    <string name="ch1Dungeon">Your first dungeon location is the _____</string>
    <string name="ch1SelectedDungeon">Your first dungeon location is the \u0020</string>
    <string name="generateDun">Generate Dungeon</string>
    <string name="ch1Enemies">The enemies in your first dungeon are _____</string>
    <string name="ch1SelectedEnemies">The enemies in your first dungeon are \u0020</string>
    <string name="chapter2quest">While on this quest the party will learn of someone who knows information about their objective, this person is _____</string>
    <string name="chapter2selectedquesthint">While on this quest the party will learn of someone who knows information about their objective, this person is \u0020</string>
    <string name="chapterTwoObjectiveRumor">However, this person has been missing from the town for several days, it is rumoured that they we\'re kidnapped and are being held by ____</string>
    <string name="chapterTwoSelectedObjectiveRumor">However, this person has been missing from the town for several days, it is rumoured that they we\'re kidnapped and are being held by \u0020</string>
    <string name="chapterTwoToChapterThreeReason">Upon rescuing their informant, they would give the party information that guides them to ____</string>
    <string name="chapterTwoSelectedEnd">Upon rescuing their informant, they would give the party information that guides them to \u0020</string>
    <string name="chapter2Objective">Your party learns of a quest from the town to ____</string>

    <string name="goblin">Goblins are strange humanoid creatures that are said to of been born from the depths of the abyss itself, often traveling in packs or warbands, they are not to be underestimated for their resourcefulness, even by the strongest of adventurers.</string>
    <string name="kobolds">Kobolds are small scaly, reptilian folk that usually hunt in packs, they are cold blooded unlike dragonfolk and are usually under the service of evil dragons, worshipping them with crude statues. </string>
    <string name="bandits">Bandits travel in gangs are usually led by bandit leaders or bandit veterans, typically bandit gangs roam the wilderness and outskirts of towns, looking for unsuspecting victims to rough up for spare coin. </string>
    <string name="wolves">Wolves are rarely seen alone, these pack predators are constantly found roaming the wilderness and occasionally can be found in caves. Many adventurer\'s have fallen to wolf ambushes. </string>
    <string name="imp">Imps are known as demon tricksters, but more often than not are known as the lackeys of warlocks and wizards or other greater demon. Imps are the rabble that while aren\'t very intimidating on their own, can be quite a hastle with their shape changing magic.</string>
    <string name="skeletons">Skeletons are said to be vengeful spirits that returned to their bodies long after their passing to enact vengeance on those who have wronged them. They are also summoned as lesser minions by necromancers and wizards to do their bidding, often against their will.</string>
    <string name="zombies">Zombies are often thralls raised from the dead by necromancers in order to carry out their bidding as meatshields and minions, often set upon innocent towns to bring back more bodies to make more zombies.</string>
    <string name="darkMage">It is said that to every light there is a shadow, evil mages are no exception to good mages, often skulking in the shadows conducting vile rituals to cause harm to the innocent.</string>


    <string name="goblinTrait">Traits: Nimble action: The goblin can hide or disengage as a bonus action every turn.</string>
    <string name="koboldTrait">Traits: Pack Tactics: The kobolds have advantage on an Attack roll if at least one of the kobold\'s allies is within 5 ft of the creature.</string>
    <string name="banditTrait">Traits: None</string>
    <string name="wolfTrait">Traits: Keen hearing and smell: Wolves have advantage on perception checks that require smelling or hearing.\nPack tactics: The wolf has advantage on any attack roll if atleast one of the wolves allies is within 5ft.  </string>
    <string name="impTrait">Traits: Shapechanger: The imp can use its action to Polymorph into a beast form that resembles a rat (speed 20 ft.), a raven (20 ft, fly 60 ft.), or a Spider (20 ft, climb 20 ft.), or back into its true form. Its Statistics are the same in each form, except for the speed changes noted. Any Equipment it is wearing or carrying isn\'t transformed. It reverts to its true form if it dies.
        \nDevil\'s Sight: Magical Darkness doesn\'t impede the imp\'s Darkvision.
        \nMagic Resistance: The imp has advantage on Saving Throws against Spells and other magical effects.
        \nVariant: Familiar: The imp can enter into a contract to serve another creature as a familiar, forming a Telepathic Bond with its willing master. While the two are bonded, the master can sense what the imp Senses as long as they are within 1 mile of each other. While the imp is within 10 feet of its master, the master shares the imp’s Magic Resistance trait. If its master violates the terms of the contract, the imp can end its service as a familiar, ending the Telepathic Bond.
        \nInvisibility: The imp magically turns Invisible until it attacks, or until its Concentration ends (as if concentrating on a spell). Any Equipment the imp wears or carries is Invisible with it.</string>
    <string name="skeletonTrait">Traits: Weakness to blunt: Takes double damage from bludgeoning damage and radiant damage.
        \nImmunities: Immune to poison, Exhaustion and takes half damage from slashing and piercing damage.</string>
    <string name="zombieTrait">Traits: Undead Fortitude: If damage reduces the zombie to 0 Hit Points, it must make a Constitution saving throw with a DC of 5+the damage taken, unless the damage is radiant or from a critical hit. On a success, the zombie drops to 1 hit point instead.
        \nImmunities: Immune to poison.</string>
    <string name="darkMageTrait">Traits: Evil Aura: Upon getting within 5Ft of the mage, make a DC10 Constitution saving through or be feared to move 5Ft backwards.\nTaste fear: Upon reducing a character to 0Hp, the dark mage feeds upon the fear of potential death, gaining temporary Hp equal to a quarter of that characters maximum Hp value.</string>

    <string name="goblinAttacks">Attacks: Melee attack: +4 to hit, reach 5ft, one target. Hit: 5 Slashing damage.\nRanged attack: +4 to hit, range 80/320 ft, one target. Hit: 5 Piercing damage.</string>
    <string name="koboldAttacks">Attacks: Melee attack: +4 to hit, reach 5ft, one target. Hit: 4 Piercing damage.\nRanged Attack: +4 to hit, reach 30/120ft, one target. Hit: 4 bludgeoning damage.</string>
    <string name="banditAttacks">Attacks: Scimitar: Melee Weapon Attack: +3 to hit, reach 5 ft, one target. Hit: 4 (1d6 + 1) slashing damage.\nLight Crossbow: Ranged Weapon Attack: +3 to hit, range 80 ft./320 ft, one target. Hit: 5 (1d8 + 1) piercing damage.</string>
    <string name="wolfAttacks">Attacks: Bite attack: +4 to hit, reach 5ft, one target. Hit: 2d4 +2 piercing damage. If the target is a living creature, it must succeed on a DC 12 Strength saving throw or be knocked prone.</string>
    <string name="impAttacks">Attacks: Sting (Bite in Beast Form): Melee Weapon Attack: +5 to hit, reach 5 ft, one target. Hit: 5 (1d4 + 4) piercing damage, and the target must make on a DC 11 Constitution saving throw, taking 10 (3d6) poison damage on a failed save, or half as much damage on a successful one.</string>
    <string name="skeletonAttacks">Attacks: Shortsword: Melee Weapon Attack: +4 to hit, reach 5 ft, one target. Hit: 5 piercing damage.
        \nShortbow: Ranged Weapon Attack: +4 to hit, range 80/320 ft, one target. Hit: 5 piercing damage.</string>
    <string name="zombieAttacks">Attacks: Slam: Melee Weapon Attack: +3 to hit, reach 5 ft, one target. Hit: 3 bludgeoning damage.</string>
    <string name="darkMageAttacks">Attacks: Quarterstaff. Melee Weapon Attack: +1 to hit, reach 5 ft, one target. Hit: 3 bludgeoning damage.
        \nEvil orb. Ranged spell attack: +2 to hit, reach 20ft, one target. Hit: 6 Arcane damage.
        \nCharm person: Ranged spell: Reach 30ft, one target. The target makes a DC13 Wisdom saving throw or be charmed on fail, the charmed target regards the caster as friendly for 2 turns and acts under the casters will or if the character makes a wisdom saving through.</string>

    <string name="goblinArmor">Armor:15\nHp:7\nSpeed:30ft</string>
    <string name="koboldArmor">Armor:12\nHp:5\nSpeed:30ft</string>
    <string name="banditArmor">Armor:12\nHp12\nSpeed:30ft</string>
    <string name="wolfArmor">Armor:13\nHp:11\nSpeed:40ft</string>
    <string name="impArmor">Armor:13\nHp:10\nSpeed:20ft, fly40ft.</string>
    <string name="skeletonArmor">Armor:13\nHp:13\nSpeed:30ft</string>
    <string name="zombieArmor">Armor:8\nHp:22\nSpeed:20ft</string>
    <string name="darkMageArmor">Armor:14\nHp25\nSpeed:30ft</string>

    <string name="goblinStats">Stats: Str-7 Dex-15 Con-11 Int-12 Wis-4 Cha-7</string>
    <string name="koboldStats">Stats: Str-7 Dex-14 Con-8 Int-7 Wis-6 Cha-7</string>
    <string name="banditStats">Stats: Str-10 Dex-13 Con-11 Int-9 Wis-10 Cha-10</string>
    <string name="wolfStats">Stats: Str-13 Dex-14 Con-13 Int-2 Wis-13 Cha-5</string>
    <string name="impStats">Stats: Str-6 Dex-18 Con-14 Int-11 Wis-12 Cha-14</string>
    <string name="skeletonStats">Stats: Str-10 Dex-13 Con-14 Int-5 Wis-7 Cha-3</string>
    <string name="zombieStats">Stats: Str-12 Dex-5 Con-15 Int-2 Wis-4 Cha-1</string>
    <string name="darkMageStats">Stats: Str-9 Dex-14 Con-12 Int-18 Wis-13</string>

    <string name="drkCave">Dark Cave</string>
    <string name="castleDungeon">Castle Dungeons</string>
    <string name="forestDungeon">Dense forest</string>
    <string name="hideoutDungeon">Secret hideout</string>

    <string name="goToLogo">Go to monster name detection</string>
    <string name="setPicture">Set name</string>
    <string name="pictureInfo">Please press the button below and take a picture of the name of the creature you want to look up! Please ensure the name is taken at the center of your camera screen and is in all Capital letters.</string>
    <string name="returnLogo">Return to monster Detection</string>
    <string name="monsterNameActivityButton">Go to Monster Name Detection</string>
    <string name="returnMain">Return To Main Menu</string>
    <string name="upload_map">Upload</string>
    <string name="download_map">Download last uploaded map</string>

    <string name="monsterCodexButton">Go to monster codex</string>
    <string name="ch2sidequest1">Help defeat the raiding bandits</string>
    <string name="ch2sidequest2">Solve a series of murder cases</string>
    <string name="ch2sidequest3">Get an animal feed shipment from the nearby farm</string>
    <string name="deleteMap">Delete Map</string>
    <string name="mainQuestHint1">The stubborn and greedy mayor.</string>
    <string name="mainQuestHint2">The leader of the town\'s brothel.</string>
    <string name="mainQuestHint3">A magical pixie living in the forest</string>
    <string name="hobgoblinDungeonch2">The hobgoblins in the nearby mountain</string>
    <string name="darkCultCh2">The dark cult in the sewers</string>
    <string name="forestDungeonCh2">The king of the forest wolves</string>
    <string name="ch2secretEscort">The a special guide who shows them the quickest path</string>
    <string name="ch2HiddenPass">A hidden passage to create a shortcut</string>
    <string name="ch2Cart">A special traveling cart for transport</string>
    <string name="prevChapter">Prev Chapter</string>
    <string name="newCampaign">New Campaign</string>
    <string name="ch3">Chapter Three</string>
    <string name="ch3StartTown">After traveling for a long while from the previous village, the party would find themselves in the new town of ____</string>
    <string name="ch3TownDisaster">After arriving in the town they would find that something tragic has befallen it, the town has been ____</string>
    <string name="ch3Informant">By sheer luck the party would find someone to give them information about the way to solve this issue, this person is a ____</string>
    <string name="ch3betrayl">Upon bringing the requested item to the informant it would be revealed that he\'s actually ____</string>
    <string name="ch3End">After a short battle with the villain, he would of managed to escape in the direction of ____</string>
    <string name="ch3TownOne">Mountain Grasp</string>
    <string name="ch3TownTwo">Icefall</string>
    <string name="ch3TownThree">Lavastone</string>
    <string name="ch3DisasterOne">cursed, most of the villagers are mind controlled!</string>
    <string name="ch3DisasterTwo">blocked by a dark barrier!</string>
    <string name="ch3DisasterThree">encased in magical ice!</string>
    <string name="ch3informantOne">wandering mercenary who instructs the party to find the gem of magic banishment.</string>
    <string name="ch3InformantTwo">mysterious hooded man who offers to teach the spell to dispell magic, at a price.</string>
    <string name="ch3InformantThree">rather strange barbarian who claims he can break the magic if he got his enchanted axe back from a nearby cave.</string>
    <string name="ch3BetrayOne">one of the demon kings lackey\'s!</string>
    <string name="ch3BetrayTwo">an assassin sent to dispatch the party, and he brought friends!</string>
    <string name="ch3BetrayThree">an adventurer driven mad by wild magic, viewing you as evil to be purged.</string>
    <string name="ch3EndOne">west.</string>
    <string name="ch3EndTwo">north.</string>
    <string name="ch3EndThree">east.</string>
    <string name="ch3SelectedTown">After traveling for a long while from the previous village, the party would find themselves in the new town of \u0020</string>
    <string name="ch3SelectedDisaster">After arriving int he town they would find that something tragic has befallen it, the town has been \u0020</string>
    <string name="ch3SelectedContact">By sheer luck the party would find someone to give them information about the way to solve this issue, this person is a \u0020</string>
    <string name="ch3SelectedBetray">Upon bringing the requested item to the informant it would be revealed that he\'s actually \u0020</string>
    <string name="ch3SelectedEnd">After a short battle with the villain, he would of managed to escape in the direction of \u0020</string>
    <string name="clear">Clear</string>
    <string name="ch4">Chapter Four</string>
    <string name="ch4start">After chasing after the villain from the previous town, the party would find themselves at ____</string>
    <string name="mapGen">Map Generation</string>
    <string name="ch4Discovery">There would be no sign of the villain personally, however the party would soon discover ____</string>
    <string name="ch4Destination">This clue would eventually lead the party to ____</string>
    <string name="ch4Battle">Upon entering their destination they would find their pursuit target in the middle of a ritual to ____</string>
    <string name="ch4End">Upon defeating the villain the party would discover a method to transport to the final destination they need to go, that method is ____</string>
    <string name="ch4beginOne">a dark stormy waterfront with an abandoned ruined port town in the distance.</string>
    <string name="ch4beginTwo">a desolate wasteland, save for a few small caves and underground burrows by some strange creature.</string>
    <string name="ch4beginThree">an oddly dense forest, its as if eyes are watching you from within the treetops.</string>
    <string name="ch4clueOne">an old tattered cloth, belonging to their target along with footprints.</string>
    <string name="ch4clueTwo">a trail of thick, black blood.</string>
    <string name="ch4clueThree">a magical rune that opens a teleport gate somewhere!</string>
    <string name="ch4localOne">a dark, dank dungeon filled with skeletons and zombies!</string>
    <string name="ch4localTwo">a high tower hidden by floating in the sky above the clouds.</string>
    <string name="ch4localThree">a deep underground cave, infested with lesser demons and kobolds.</string>
    <string name="ch4battleOne">summon a lich to assist them, must be stopped within 5 turns!</string>
    <string name="ch4battleTwo">summon a flock of lesser imps to assist, must be stopped in 2 turns.</string>
    <string name="ch4battleThree">empower himself with the dark magic of his master, must be stopped in 3 turns.</string>
    <string name="ch4endOne">the ritual portal activating again, revealing a portal to the item they seek\'s dungeon.</string>
    <string name="ch4endThree">that upon defeating the villain, the ritual portal spat out several lesser demons under the control of the first hero they see, able to fly the party to their destination.</string>
    <string name="ch4endTwo">that the party would find a scroll of teleportation in the villain\'s backpack, able to transport the party to wherever they wish with one use.</string>
    <string name="ch4SelectedStart">After chasing after the villain from the previous town, the party would find themselves at \u0020</string>
    <string name="ch4SelectedClue">There would be no sign of the villain personally, however the party would soon discover \u0020</string>
    <string name="ch4SelectedLocal">This clue would eventually lead the party to \u0020</string>
    <string name="ch4SelectedRitual">Upon entering their destination they would find their pursuit target in the middle of a ritual to \u0020</string>
    <string name="ch4SelectedEnd">Upon defeating the villain the party would discover a method to transport to the final destination they need to go, that method is \u0020</string>
    <string name="ch5Start">(At this point in the campaign it is not 100% necessary to follow the text, the labyrinth is huge, so please explore at your leisure if you wish and make up as you go.) The party would arrive at their final destination, a long sprawling dungeon of great depth, it would be hard to see ahead in the darkness, but there would be three directions to go, they are ____</string>
    <string name="mapSelect">Map Selection</string>
    <string name="townMapGen">Town Map Generation</string>
    <string name="worldMapGen">World Map Generation</string>
    <string name="labyrinthMapGen">Labyrinth Map Generation</string>
    <string name="ch5Encounter">Upon taking the first turn the party would be suddenly ambushed from both sides by ____</string>
    <string name="ch5Turn">After successfully defending themselves against hte ambush, the party would find that something has changed within the dungeon, that change is ____</string>
    <string name="ch5FinalBoss">(Only start this once your satisfied with exploration) As the party emerges from the next room they would find that their target is awaiting them in the next room! That target being ____</string>
    <string name="ch5End">As the foul adversary is defeated once and for all, and the treasure claimed, the party can finally return home and retire for now, the treasure being split up and the party would ___</string>
    <string name="ch5start1">north, a lit path.</string>
    <string name="ch5start2">east, a dim dark path.</string>
    <string name="ch5start3">west, a path that looks like the walls are crumbling.</string>
    <string name="ch5Encounter1">skeleton marauders!</string>
    <string name="ch5Encounter2">zombie thralls!</string>
    <string name="ch5Encounter3">fire imps!</string>
    <string name="ch5turn1">a teleport rune appeared underneath the party, warping them to the center of the labyrinth.</string>
    <string name="ch5turn2">a hidden passageway opened up, leading to the labyrinth treasury.</string>
    <string name="ch5turn3">a pitfall trap opens up under the party, sending them into the labyrinth\'s waterway.</string>
    <string name="ch5boss1">the dark lord, Railak the terrible!</string>
    <string name="ch5boss2">the great warlock of the labyrinth, Kozlik.</string>
    <string name="ch5boss3">the evil wizard, Illath who used an ancient artifact to transform into a black dragon!</string>
    <string name="ch5end1">go their separate ways on their own adventures.</string>
    <string name="ch5end2">return home together and become lords and kings of their homeland.</string>
    <string name="ch5end3">set out on another adventure somewhere, adventure awaits those who look!</string>
    <string name="ch5endthanks">Thank you so much for using my application for this campaign, I hope you enjoyed it!</string>
    <string name="ch5SelectedStart">The party would arrive at their final destination, a long sprawling dungeon of great depth, it would be hard to see ahead in the darkness, but there would be three directions to go, they are \u0020</string>
    <string name="ch5SelectedEncounter">Upon taking the first turn the party would be suddenly ambushed from both sides by \u0020</string>
    <string name="ch5SelectedTurn">After successfully defending themselves against hte ambush, the party would find that something has changed within the dungeon, that change is \u0020</string>
    <string name="ch5SelectedBoss">As the party emerges from the next room they would find that their target is awaiting them in the next room! That target being \u0020</string>
    <string name="ch5SelectedEnd">As the foul adversary is defeated once and for all, and the treasure claimed, the party can finally return home and retire for now, the treasure being split up and the party would \u0020</string>
    <string name="ch1enemey1">goblins</string>
    <string name="ch1enemy2">kobolds</string>
    <string name="ch1enemy3">bandits</string>
    <string name="ch1enemy4">wolves</string>
</resources>
